<?xml version="1.0" ?><FundaRoot><FLoot title = "Introduction" id="1" imagename="0f139462c00d2c7253b9883b6a6dd81b" priorityset= "1" isweblink= "0" fileext=".jpg"><![CDATA[- COJOU -   Is the guild light of forming the nature. We specialize in the manufacture of all sorts of necklaces, cabochons, handbags, silvers and  rosaries. The material we adopt the most is  black coral. We also adopt material other than black coral, for instance black golden coral, sponge coral and all sorts of other corals.  Experience in making handcraft products is the  most important aspect of our company. With  thirty five years experience in the handcraft industry, we can guarantee every single one of our items to be of outstanding quality. There is no artificial material used in our products, because we believe that the natural formation produces perfect jewelry. Our manufacturing process is effective and  efficient. We can boast a 100% credit rating  and guarantee on-time delivery. A sample can be provided upon request and will be sent via post. For more information please contact us.]]></FLoot><SLoot title = "contact" id="2" imagename="47ed10ade297311460620d8a692181ee" priorityset= "2" isweblink= "0" fileext=".jpg"><![CDATA[<b>Taiwan:</b>

prochiang@gmail.com

Fax: 886-2-2984-8579]]></SLoot><TLoot title = "support" id="6" imagename="1c663f4dbd856b57e6f1d9e394c27ea3" priorityset= "3" isweblink= "0" fileext=".jpg"><![CDATA[The major composition of coral is carbolic calcium. Try to avoid the following as much 
as possible while wearing this ornament:

1.	Sweat
2.	Acid
3.	Soap
4.	Seawater
5.	Greasy dirt
6.	Other Chemical composition (for instance, Alkali)

All the components above will cause damaged to the surface of the coral. It is also a good idea not to wear it while taking a bath or spa.

<b>REGULAR MAINTENANCE:</b>

Please wash coral with cool or warm water and then use a soft cloth to wipe it dry. The best maintenance for larger sized carvings is having it in glass or any transparent container to avoid both dirt and direct sunshine. If it gets dirty, the simplest ways to solve this problem is by using a woolen brush, brush it slightly and then use a soft cloth to wipe it up.

In the case of serious damage, consult a professional.(Note: For more information please contact us by e-mail.]]></TLoot></FundaRoot>